谁想让自己的蛋蛋爽一爽
Who wants their balls crushed?
我
Me.
不是你们想的那样
This isn't what it looks like.
前情提要
你走人吧 拿上你的东西滚蛋吧
You're done. Grab your shit and get the fuck out.
- 英雄克星是我的 - 你这是一个垂死之人最后一次吹牛
-The Boys is mine. -Says a dying man with one last bluff.
超级七人队会更加强大 为鞭炮热烈鼓掌吧
The Seven is getting even stronger. Put your hands together for Firecracker.
我做了什么让你这么恨我
What have I done to make you hate me so much?
你真的不记得我了 是吗
You really don't remember me, do you?
和智者姐妹
And Sister Sage!
法西斯
Fascist!
她是“世界上最聪明的人”
She's the world's smartest person.
你很性感
你还记得科林豪瑟吗
You remember Colin Hauser?
他发现你谋杀了他家人时会怎样
So, what happens when he finds out you murdered his family?
我爸爸 他中风了
My dad, he had a stroke.
- 我真的很抱歉 休伊 - 妈
- I'm really sorry. Really. - Mom?
我想策反火车头
I want to flip A-Train.
火车头的内心摇摆不定 时机已经成熟了
He's right there, he's ready.
够了
Enough!
除非超越人性 否则你永远也不会成为真正的自己
You're never gonna be your true self until you transcend your humanity.
你需要回到起点
You need to go back to the start.
你需要回家
You need to go home.
祖国人 1987
嘿 马蒂
Hey, Marty.
楼上的监控摄像头突然断了信号
The security cameras upstairs just went black.
无信号
菲尔 听到了吗
Hey, Phil, you copy?
菲尔
Phil?
上面有人吗
Anyone up there?
打电话给沃特 告诉他们有人闯进来了
Call Vought, tell them we have a breach.
线路不通
The line's dead.
卡维尔 全美最鲜的冰淇淋
大家好
Hello, everyone.
- 嘿 - 嗨
Hi.
- 约翰  - 祖国人
John. - Homelander.
就叫祖国人
Just Homelander.
马蒂 见到你真好
Hey, Marty. Good to see you.
- 我也是 祖国人 - 好
You, too, uh, Homelander.
天哪 感觉真离奇
Oh, my God, this is just so surreal.
从没想过我会回到这里
I never thought I'd be back here.
勾起太多的回忆了
So many memories.
我带来了鲸鱼弗吉冰淇淋蛋糕
Oh, I, uh, I brought a Fudgie the Whale.
帮个忙 拿个盘子和一些叉子来 好吗
Do me a favor, could you get a plate and some forks?
太感谢了
Thank you so much.
我看到了一些新面孔
I see some new faces.
但很多人我都认得出来 弗兰克
But a lot that I recognize. Frank.
马蒂已经当上助理主任了吧
And-and Assistant Director now, Marty.
我还记得那时 他们让你去擦装粪便样本的容器
I still remember when they had you wiping out the stool sample containers.
记得吗
You remember?
是啊
Yeah.
芭芭拉呢
Where's Barbara?
- 据我所知 她还在当主任 - 她今天不在
-Last I checked, she's still Director? -She's off-site today.
让她来 好吗 我很想叙叙旧
Oh, bring her in, would you? I'd love to catch up.
告诉她这是一次小聚会
Tell her-- Tell her it's a little reunion.
很好 大家都来吃吧
Terrific. All right, everyone, dig in.
来吧 别不好意思 不然就化了
Come on, don't be shy. Before it melts.
家 甜蜜的家
来嘛 快来 这就对了嘛
Please. Come on in. There you go.
英雄克星
第四季第四集
本WEB版外挂字幕由  风吹来的那片云  双语合并
你在干什么
What are you doing?
快起来
Come on, get up.
布彻尔 世界并不会 因为你糟糕的人生终结而终结
Butcher, the world doesn't end just because your shitty life does.
起来
Get up.
开什么玩笑
Are you fucking kidding me?!
抱歉 你父亲的情况 符合脑死亡的标准
I'm sorry, your father's condition meets the criteria for brain death.
也许看起来不人道 但这却是最人道的事情
It might not seem like it, but it is the most humane thing.
人道 你要撤掉饲管 让他饿死 对吧
Humane? You're pulling his feeding tubes so he starves to death, right?
休伊 他想要这样
Hughie, it's what he wanted.
还有多久他就...
How long before, um...
最多几天
A couple of days at most.
妈
Mom.
不要
Don't.
对不起
I'm sorry.
休伊
Hughie...
V52博览会 与超级七人队见面
V52 Expo. Come meet The Seven in person,
独享一睹《训练》的机会...
and get an exclusive sneak peek of Training A-Tr--
今晚 东部时间8点 中部时间7点 请收看《真相》之...
Tonight, 8:00/7:00 Central on The Whole Truth...
在校园被血洗的暴行之后
After their bloody campus rampage,
玛丽莫罗和其他 四个戈多尔金大学的学生
Marie Moreau and the other Godolkin Four have seemingly vanished
似乎落入了一个黑暗的大洞里 消失不见...
into a dark, gaping hole.
因新宣布的反超级英雄立法
With his newly announced anti-Superhero legislation,
鲍勃辛格尔刚刚向美国人民 展露了其真实面目
Bob Singer has just shown the American people who he really is.
一个法西斯分子 想用铁拳统治...
A deranged fascist hellbent on ruling the country...
你应该听听他们对我的评价
You should hear what they say about me.
超级英雄冒着...
请让我们私下谈谈
Give us the room.
詹纽艾瑞小姐 我唯一真正想听到的是
Miss January, the only thing I really want to hear is
“我们找到了 杀死这个得意忘形的贱人的方法”
"We found a way to kill the head-popping bitch."
- 那恐怕我们没什么好谈的 - 您需要我的帮助 先生
-Then this will be a quick meeting. -You need my help, sir.
我读了您控制超人类法案的草案
I read the draft of your Supe-control bill.
让我猜猜 它很完美 你却知道怎样修改它
Let me guess, it's perfect, but you know just how to fix it.
如果法案通过 那相当于木桩直插沃特的心脏
If you get it passed, that's a stake through Vought's heart.
让他们离开军队 警察部门 让他们股价大跌 让他们陷入诉讼
Gets 'em out of the military, policing, tanks their stock, buries 'em in lawsuits.
听起来我着实不需要你的帮助
See, it sure sounds like I don't need your help.
但只有法案通过 那些才会实现
But that's if you get it passed.
五千万选民要求国会立即作为 你做得到吗
You need-- what?-- 50 million constituents demanding Congress get off its ass?
无意冒犯 但您的公关部门有点不给力
No offense, but your PR department is kind of shitting the bed.
我刚刚才批准了巨额的推广费用
I just okayed a huge marketing spend.
在《犯罪现场调查:拉斯维加斯》 节目中插播广告
Yeah, your ad-buys during CSI: Las Vegas are definitely winning over
怎么比得上多频道的轮番轰炸
the "left the TV on 'cause they're dead" demo.
那么
So,
你有什么建议
what is your suggestion?
我可以让全国各地的人们走上街头
I can get people into the streets all over the country,
他们会要求该法案获得通过
and they'll demand that the bill gets passed.
- 以星光的身份吗  - 是的
- You'll do it as Starlight? - Yes.
如果有必要的话
I'll even make another fucking...
我甚至会再做一套该死的战衣
Supersuit if I have to.
你想获得什么回报
And what do you get for this?
一个承诺而已
Just a promise.
答应我你会完成自己开始的事情
Promise me you'll finish what you started.
一劳永逸地
Once and for all...
我们埋葬沃特
we put Vought into the ground.
亲爱的 这是什么歌
Colin, what is this?
你不是很有文化吗
Oh, who's uncultured now?
《哭泣的时间》雷查尔斯
雷查尔斯 这是他 西部乡村音乐时期的唱片
Ray Charles, his country western phase.
我爸以前经常在车里放这首歌
My dad used to play this all the time in the car,
而我会在后座上睡着
and I'd fall asleep to it in the backseat.
你从来没有 告诉过我关于他们的事情
You never told me about them.
你的家人
Your family.
我...
It's, uh...
不是很想讲述那段经历
not exactly my favorite story to tell.
不 亲爱的 不用说的
No. Désolé.
没事
No, it's fine.
我妈妈在业余时间辅导我学习
When my mom wasn't on my ass for my grades,
但她的工作是联邦法官
she was a federal judge.
她处理过非常暴力的案件 最暴力的案件
She dealt with really violent cases, like, the worst of the worst.
有一个俄罗斯黑手党 在布莱顿海滩活动
And there was this Russian mafia thing in Brighton Beach.
他们的老大是个女人
Their boss was this woman.
我妈妈要用她以儆效尤
My mom was gonna make an example out of her.
所以 他们就杀害了我妈以儆效尤
So they made an example out of my mom.
某些人闯入我家 他们先找到了我的父母
Some guy broke in, and they found my parents first.
然后是我的小妹妹
Then my little sister.
当时你在场
You were there?
枪声把我吵醒了
The gunshots woke me up.
我听到他从走廊走来 就躲在了床底下
I heard 'em coming down the hallway, so I just hid under my bed.
我只看到了他的脚踝
All I saw was his ankle.
他有伤疤 或者可能是烧伤
He had these scars, or these burns maybe.
总会在噩梦中重现这些场景
Ugh, a lot of nightmares about those.
对不起
I'm sorry.
吃早餐吗
Breakfast?
你好吗
Hey, how are you?
嗨 珍妮特
Hey, Janet.
你们好 叫史黛西和马克来吧
Hey, guys, let's call in Stacey and Mark.
我们需要准备一份公告
We need to get an announcement ready.
怎么了
What?
他们在做什么
What are they doing?
沃特新闻
鞭炮带你看真相
儿童自由斗士
那个贱人
That bitch.
沃特新闻网正在为鞭炮 搞节目的启动仪式
VNN is handling the launch of Firecracker's show,
所有沃特的媒体网络都将进行联播
simulcast across all Vought networks.
网络喷子们已经在挖掘 各种关于星光的负面素材
The troll farms are already digging up fringe anti-Starlight content
并将其注入主流媒体
and injecting it into the mainstream.
目前 “星光的进步圣战”
So far, "Starlight's Progressive Jihad"
和标签“傲慢的白人女权主义” 势头强劲
and "#ArrogantWhiteFeminism" are showing promise.
我们需要算法 来找到最容易接受这些内容的用户
We need the algorithm to find the most receptive users,
将文章在其社媒的订阅页面上置顶
then blast the articles to the top of their social feeds
直到一亿人不明所以地
until 100 million people are outraged by Starlight
对星光感到愤怒难抑
for reasons they can't even explain.
厉害
Dope.
英雄们 你们有各自的谈话要点
Heroes, you have your talking points,
大家各司其职吧
so, everyone, get to it.
- 我们可以谈谈吗  - 不可以
- Hey, can we talk? - No.
我在想 午餐时
Hey. So, I was thinking over lunch
我们可以点些风味小镇的油炸泡菜
we could order some of those fried pickles from Flavortown,
或者直接去比目鱼庞德尔 吃特别推荐菜肴
or just skip straight to the flounder pounder special.
我发现在某种程度上 你令人厌恶的程度无法量化
I find you repulsive in a way that's difficult to quantify.
而在量化方面 我他妈的十分在行 所以...
And I'm fucking amazing at quantifying, so...
大日子
So, big day.
准备好了吗
You ready?
充分得超出你的想象
You have no idea.
- 我这辈子一直都在等待这一刻 - 最后一招
-I've been waiting for this my whole life. -One last piece of the puzzle.
我想你用这个 可能会有个精彩的收场
Figured this could be your big finish.
第一次见到你时 我觉得你有点傲慢
You know, when I first met you, I thought you were kind of uppity,
但其实你是个好人
but you're one of the good ones.
我们都是超级七人队的新成员嘛
Well, we are the new kids in The Seven.
得互相照顾
Gotta look out for each other.
美国
爱国者们 大家好
Hello, Patriots!
我知道 可能你们当中有很多人 都是通过我的播客认识我的
Now, I know a lot of you probably know me from my podcast,
但在接下来的六个小时里 沃特新闻网给了我平台
but VNN gave me the next six hours to bring you the truth
让我告诉你们 星光和她的“恐怖”之家的真相
about Starlight and her house of horrors. Where dozens of trafficked children...
包拿好了吗
Here, grab your bags and come with me.
亲爱的 你忘了这个 拿上
- Sweetheart, don't forget this. Here you go. - Okay.
我们从后门偷偷地把孩子们带出去
- We'll sneak the kids out through the back. - Okay.
你确定吗
Are you sure about this?
确定 请告诉萨莎 别过多地使用客房服务 好吗
Yeah. Just please tell Sasha to have them go easy on the room service, okay?
那张卡快刷爆了
That card is almost maxed out.
- 没问题 - 谢谢
- You got it. - Thank you.
鞭炮的名人朋友们来了
Firecracker's celebrity friends are arriving.
我看到乔恩沃伊特了
I saw Jon Voight.
他妈的 他怎么来了
What the fuck is he doing here?
我要他回来
Bringing him back in.
不行 我不信任他
No. No, no, no, no, no. I don't trust him.
就是不信任他 如果让他回来 你就是疯了 好吗
I don't. And you're insane if you do, okay?
无论你经历了何种痛苦 都可以酒醉而死
And you can drink yourself to death in whatever dark hole you crawled out of.
- 好主意 我可能会照办 - 很好
-That's a good idea. I might just do that. -Good.
等一下 等等 布彻尔
Okay, wait a minute. Hold on a second, Butcher.
天地明鉴 我对这个家伙有看法 我们俩都对他有看法
Look, Lord knows I got problems with the guy, too
但这事超越了你我的个人意见
We both do, but this is bigger than us.
祖国人和智者谈论的计划
That shit Homelander and Sage are talking about,
会引发世界末日的
that's some end-of-time shit.
他可能是个混蛋 但他是团队的一员 我们需要这个混蛋
Team is shy one total asshole. Now, we need this motherfucker.
- 母乳... - 安妮 这是我的决定 没得商量
- I mean, I'm... - Annie, this is my call. It's done.
那好吧
Well, all right then.
我很高兴我们解决了这个问题
Happy we got that sorted, eh?
谁能跟我解释一下
Now, can someone please explain to me
为什么鞭炮把你当成进攻目标
what makes you Firecracker's Moby Cunt?
- 我不知道 - 胡说八道
- I have no idea. - Bollocks.
真不知道
I don't.
那我们的下一步行动是什么
Now, what's our next move?
你跟上头给我要五万美金 三个小时内
You get me 50K from the Company, and in three hours
我就会准备好 对付这位“枪炮小姐”所需要的猛料
I'll have all the dirt we need on Little Miss Guns and Ammo.
布彻尔 我不可能让你 带着五万美金离开我的视线
Butcher, there's no way I'm letting you out of my sight with 50 grand.
好吧 但我警告你
All right. But I'm warning you,
我做的事 你不会喜欢的
you ain't gonna like it.
还有坎耶维斯特
And Kanye West!
但首先请看以西结的布道
But first, a sermon by Ezekiel,
在星光失去上帝的恩典之前 他是她童年的牧师
Starlight's childhood pastor before she fell from God's grace.
马上回来为您奉上细节 请不要走开
We'll be right back with that, y'all. You stick around.
美国
U.S.A.!
弗兰克 过来
Hey, Frank, come on over.
来一场废纸篮球赛怎么样
How about a game of wastepaper basketball?
什么
I'm sorry?
谁先投进三球谁赢 这么着吧 让游戏变得有趣点
Uh, first of three, and tell you what, make it interesting,
你赢了 我就让你早点下班 去见家人
you win, I'll let you knock off early, go see the fam.
好的
Um, okay.
很好 我先投
Excellent. I'll start.
这个游戏是我跟你学的 弗兰克
You know, I learned this game from you, Frank.
我不明白
I don't understand.
有一次 我看到你朝废纸篓扔东西
I once saw you take a shot at a waste basket,
你投进了 然后...
and you nailed it, and...
可你不记得
and you don't remember.
- 不记得 - 这个嘛
-No. -Yeah, well,
我可记得很清楚呢
I sure do.
你坐在那里 而我就在这个炉子里
Yeah, you were sitting there, and, well, I was in this oven here.
投中时 你还轻握拳头庆祝呢
And you made the shot. You did a little fist pump to celebrate,
然后 你调高了炉温 看自己是否会灼伤我的皮肤
and then you turned up the temperature to see if you could burn my skin.
这事你还记得吧
You remember that, right?
该你了
Your turn.
有趣的是 尽管我的皮肤没有烧焦
Fun fact. Um, even though my skin didn't char,
但仍然感到很痛
it still really hurt.
我是说 非常痛
I mean a lot.
我当时就在炉子里
Yeah, I was in there,
痛苦地尖叫
screaming in agony,
眼泪立刻就嘶嘶地汽化了
and my tears just sizzled away.
是的
Yeah.
我记得
I remember there was,
有好多人站在这里做记录
uh, people standing here taking notes,
但越过他们 我看到你把东西投进了纸篓
but behind them I saw you make that shot.
那一投棒极了 弗兰克
It really was a great shot, Frank.
我只是在做自己的工作
I was just doing my job.
那一刻让我做了很多噩梦
You know, I had nightmares about that exact moment,
可你甚至都不记得这件事了
and you can't even remember it.
很可笑 不是吗 对于...
It's funny, isn't it,
完全相同的事情 人们居然
how people can have such a different memory
能有截然不同的记忆
of the exact same thing.
我想都是因为视角不同吧
It's all a matter of perspective, I guess.
弗兰克
Hey, Frank?
这是我最后一投了 不如你去那边看着吧
This is my last shot. Why don't you go watch from in there?
- 约翰 不如我们... - 叫我祖国人
- John, why don't we-- -"Homelander."
- 进炉子 弗兰克 - 求你了
- Get in the oven, Frank. - Please.
进炉子 否则你的家人会和你一起进去
Get in the oven or your family goes in with you.
- 拜托 你不必这样做 - 马蒂
- Please, Homelander, you don't have to do this. - Marty.
谢谢
Thank you.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我非常抱歉
I'm so, so sorry.
你抱歉
You're sorry?
现在
Now?
为什么
But why?
你只是在做自己的工作 对吧
You were just doing your job, right?
不 不要啊 救命 不
Don't do this! No.
我打赌你本会赢的
And I bet you would've won.
我的天哪
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
我原谅你
I forgive you.
你的联系人在哪
不知道 他应该很快就到
Uh, I don't know, he should be here any minute.
顺便说一句 谢谢你为我保驾护航
Thanks, by the way, for being my muscle.
这里真臭 味道像腐烂的鱼鸭
鸡巴 鱼鸡巴
是的
Yeah.
搞什么鬼
What the shit is this?
戴着金链子 长着山羊胡的话痨哪去了
Where's the talking goatee with the gold chains?
没关系 是我打给你的
It's okay. I'm the one that called you.
你疯了吗
Are you crazy?
智者在盯着我 巴不得我露出马脚呢
Sage is on my ass, stares at me like I'm fucking dinner.
你居然认为现在是见面的好时机
But you thought this was a good time to be seen together?
我需要一剂五号化合物 今天就需要
I need a dose of Compound V, and I need it today.
就这事 为什么
Is that all? For what?
你在乎个什么劲儿
What do you care?
祖国人让人把所有的五号化合物 都锁在他的公寓里了
Homelander has every vial of V locked up in his apartment.
有好几百瓶 谁也拿不到
- Hundreds of them. Nobody gets it. Okay.
那么 一瓶不见了对他来说无所谓 你必须想出个办法
Well, he's not gonna miss one vial, then. You got to find a way.
不行 太危险了
No. It's too dangerous.
不 嘿 去他的 你欠我人情
No, hey. Fuck that! You owe me.
我欠你人情  我才刚他妈的救过你的命
I owe you? I just saved your fucking life.
发生在我身上 我们所有人身上的 每一件倒霉的事 可怕的事
Every single fucked up, horrible thing that's ever happened to me, to all of us,
都是由你一手造成的
it all started with you,
因为你夺走了我爱的人
'cause you took away someone I loved.
- 你要把我爱的人还给我 - 什么
-And now you're gonna give someone I love back. -What?
我爸快要死了
My dad's about to die.
只有五号化合物才能救他
V is the only thing that can save him.
这是你...
This is your chance...
矫枉的机会
...to finally make things right.
为什么你会觉得我在乎这档子事
What makes you think I give a shit?
我不知道 你告诉我
You tell me.
如果我帮你
If I do this...
我们就两清了
we're good?
永远两清了
Forever?
是的
Yes.
怎么了
What?
你可没说我们要见火车头 另外 你居然想要五号
你还没吸取教训吗
喜美子 对不起 但那是我爸 我还能有什么办法
Kimiko, I'm sorry, but it's my dad. What else was I supposed to do?
对不起 但我认为你应该让你爸死
搞什么
该死
Fuck!
搞什么鬼
那些家伙是谁
Who the fuck are those guys?
不行 我动不了 我的脚踝
No, I can't. I can't. My ankle.
不 天哪
No, no, no. Oh, Jesus.
那些家伙是谁
Who the fuck are those guys?
光 真理之光 光...闪光
Light. Shining Light? Like-- Shining Light. Shining Light?
他们为什么追我们
Why are they after us?
我杀了他们一伙人
该死
Fuck.
那我们怎么办
Okay, what do we do?
跑 回到货车上
不行 我跑不了 我做不来
No, I-I can't run anywhere. I can't.
我不知道
No, no, no.
放松点 好吧
Easy. All right.
好吧
Okay.
我懂了
I got it.
想救你爸吗 要么战斗 要么死掉
爱让我们找到归宿
? Love lift us up where we belong ?
老鹰哭泣的地方
? Where the eagles cry ?
在山上...
? On a mountain...
危险 液氮 切勿接触 极度低温
五万美金的事
Not a word about that 50 grand
还有用它干了什么 全都要对马洛里守口如瓶 混蛋
and what happened to it to Mallory, motherfucker.
都给网络写手了
Straight up Webweaver's stinky spider?
海洛因灌肠剂可不便宜 哥们儿
Heroin enemas don't come cheap, my son.
我永远无法忽视那些鸟事
I'll never unsee that nasty shit.
我他妈的不是警告过你了吗
Well, I fucking warned you, didn't I?
总之呢 无所谓的 我们需要的东西到手了 搞定
Anyway, don't matter. Got what we needed. Job done.
你能告诉我 脸上的伤口是怎么搞的吗
You ever gonna tell me what happened with that gash on your face?
各位 掌声有请...
M 我有件事想请你帮忙
M, I got a favor to ask.
你认为自己有资格要我帮忙吗
Think you're in a position to ask for a favor?
如果我临死还没搞定这事
If I can't get the job done before I, uh...
我需要你把莱恩从祖国人手上救出来
I need you to get Ryan away from Homelander.
布彻尔
Oh, Butcher.
我得...现实一点
I got to be realistic.
有些时候 我他妈的真感觉挨不下去了
Some days I can barely even fucking stand.
带他离开沃特 把他养大
Get him out of there. Raise him.
把他养大
Raise him?
你是我所知的最好的父亲 M
You're the best dad I know, M.
最他妈好的人
The best fucking anyone.
这是你对我说过的最好听的话之一
That might be one of the nicest things you've ever said to me, but...
但如果莱恩不想离开呢
what if Ryan doesn't want to go?
那你就得逼他离开
Then you've got to make him.
白人垃圾走过去了
White trash walking.
表演得真是一流 亲爱的
Top-notch show, love.
只是不确定你是想让我们 跪在你的十字架前 还是把它烧掉
Just weren't sure whether you wanted us to kneel before your cross or burn it.
你们就是那些杀了我朋友的混蛋
Oh, you're those motherfuckers that killed my friend.
哎呀 真是不好意思了
Yeah, crying shame, that.
希望这么说能给你点安慰
此时此刻 他与上帝同在 正在品尝上帝的至圣之物
But if it's any consolation, he's up there with God, noshing on his holiest of holies as we speak.
我他妈的要给你颜色看...
I'm gonna shut your fucking face--
得了 稳着点吧 亲爱的
All right, all right. Keep your hair on, love.
我们只是想跟你聊聊而已
We just want a little chin wag's all.
- 说美国英语 - 对哦
- Talk American. - Right.
你还记得28岁那年神奇的夏天吗
You remember that magical summer when you was 28,
你在佛罗里达州
working as a counselor at the Capes
戴维的基督圣经夏令营担任辅导员
for Christ Bible Camp in Davie, Florida,
遇到了那个让你心动的15岁男孩
and you met that lovely 15-year-old boy
后来不只是心动了而已吧
who tickled your fancy, and, well, then, tickled more than that, didn't he?
回忆起什么没
Ring any bells?
这是布劳沃德县 治安部门拍摄的一张小纪念品
Here's a little keepsake snapped by the Broward County Sheriff's Department
你可以把它存在自己的手淫照片库里
that you can stash in your wank bank.
你和你的小白脸儿
You and your little Bieber edging
在餐厅的停车场车震 在你车的后座上翻云覆雨
in the back of your RAV4 in the car park of Buca di Beppo.
无论你的律师采取什么措施 来撤销对你的法定指控
Whatever voodoo Vought's lawyers pulled to get your statutory charges dropped,
你的福音派听众并不会在乎
I don't think they're gonna matter too much to your evangelical audience back there.
告诉我们你对智者和其宏伟计划
You're gonna tell us everything you know
所掌握的一切情况
about Sage and her grand plan,
不然我就点一下 “发送推文”的小按钮
or I hit this little tweet button here.
不如我自己发好了
How about I just send it myself?
闯了祸再说
Fuck around and find out.
星光的名字包含九个字母
"Starlight." That's nine letters,
或者是倒过来的六
or is that six... upside down?
安妮詹纽艾瑞包含十二个字母 也就是两个六
"Annie January," 12 letters, that's two more sixes.
三个六 魔鬼的标志 还需要什么证据
6-6-6. What more proof could you possibly need?
对不起 我得打断一下 非常抱歉
I'm sorry, I got to interrupt. I'm so sorry.
我需要忏悔
I need, I need to make a confession.
忏悔
A confession?
我需要忏悔我的罪孽
I need to confess my sins.
这件事无法粉饰 我...
Ain't no way to sugarcoat this. I had...
和一个可爱的年轻人
...inappropriate relations
发生了不正当关系
with a sweet young man.
该死 他的笑容太迷人了
Damn, that smile.
但那个年轻人
But that young man,
他当时15岁
he was 15 years old.
但我的意志最薄弱的时刻
But the moment of my greatest weakness was also the moment
也是将我推向永恒救赎的一刻
that pushed me to my eternal salvation.
我重生了
I was born again,
我的罪孽被上帝
and my sins were washed away
爱的泪水涤荡一净
by the tears of His love.
赞美主
Praise the Lord! Praise the Lord!
现在 我相信我主耶稣基督
Now, I-I believe that our Lord Jesus Christ put
让我在有生之年遇到那个年轻男孩
that young man in my life to lead me
是要将我引向正义之路
to the path of righteousness.
我的天哪
Oh, my God.
你得选择沐浴上帝之爱的光芒
You got to choose to turn in to the light of His love.
而星光恰恰没有这样做
And that's what Starlight, she just didn't do.
你们都听说过 她第一次救人的故事吗
Y'all ever hear that story about her very first save?
她当时只有13岁
She was only 13 years old,
一名枪手进入沃尔玛 劫持了人质
and, well, a gunman came into Walmart and took hostages.
星光进了超市 英勇得很
Well, Starlight, she came in a'blasting.
但他们没有告诉你们
But what they don't tell you
那天她把一位人质弄瞎了
is that she blinded one of those hostages that day.
这位三个孩子的母亲 只是去商店给孩子买糖而已
A mother of three, just trying to buy Crunch Berries for her kids.
但是 星光
But Starlight,
她不管不顾地对着镜头微笑
she just went on, smiling for those cameras
就像这些事都没有发生过一样
like none of it ever happened.
星光并不是英雄
Starlight's no hero.
从来都不是
She never was.
我那时还在学习 如何控制自己的超能力 我...
I was still learning how to control my powers, I...
安妮小姐
Mademoiselle Annie.
无论你们尝试了什么
Well, whatever you attempted,
看来是失败了
it seems you have failed.
话别说得太早了 法兰奇
Not so fast, Frenchie.
鞭炮拖车的钥匙
Keys to her trailer.
去搜搜看吧
Go give it a toss, will you?
火车头
A-Train.
你他妈的在做什么
What the fuck are you doing here?
拿五号化合物是吧
Taking V, huh?
- 你他妈的在做什么  - 什么也没做
-What the hell are you doing in here? -Nothing.
你在他的马桶里拉了一泡屎
You left a floater in his toilet?
我到这里时 马桶里就有屎
That was there when I got here.
这是我见过的最可悲的回击
That is the most pathetic clapback that I have ever seen.
知道吧 如果祖国人知道了 以后你就没命拉屎了
And you know, if Homelander knew, that'll be the last shit you ever take.
是吗 如果祖国人知道 你拿了五号 他会活剥你的皮
Oh, yeah? If Homelander knew you took that V, he would flay you alive.
看来我们俩都有麻烦了
Looks like we both have a problem.
看来确实如此
Looks like we do.
那我们该怎么办呢
So, what do we do about it?
1米77 祖国人 16岁
- 马蒂 过来一下 - 什么事
- Marty. Come here for a sec. - Yeah?
我想道歉
I'd like to apologize.
为弗兰克的事道歉
For Frank.
我觉得自己刚才有点脾气暴躁
Look, I guess I-I got a little grumpy,
我很抱歉
and I-I'm sorry.
你能原谅我吗
Can you forgive me?
当然
Of course.
这些事情...这些事情总会发生
These things, these things happen.
谢谢
Thank you.
你一直是最善良的人之一
You were always one of the kinder ones.
- 是的 约翰 - 祖国人
- That's right, John. -"Homelander."
祖国人 我们以前是朋友
Homelander. We were friends.
我一直都对你很好
I was always nice to you.
没错 确实是的
Yeah, that's right.
大部分时候
You were. Mostly.
你还记得你给我起的绰号 对吧
Well, you remember the nickname you had for me, right?
不会忘了吧
Really?
射精小子
"Squirt."
是的 你叫我射精小子 傻瓜
Yeah, you called me Squirt, silly.
你还记得为什么吗
You remember why?
- 不记得 - 马蒂 好吧
-No. -Oh, f-- Marty, okay.
但你确实记得我曾被关在那儿
But you do remember, though, that I used to be left in there
一关就是几个小时 甚至几天
for hours, days on end.
完全是独自一人 对吧
Completely alone. Right?
不过 我从来都不是 真正地独自一人 不是吗
Only... I was never really alone, was I?
一直有人盯着呢
Big Brother was always watching.
你一直都在盯着 不是吗 马蒂
You were always watching, weren't you, Marty?
不过
But...
未成年的男孩有一定的需求 可以这样说吧
growing boys have... certain needs, shall we say?
所以 我发现你结束了晚上的巡视后
So I figured out that when you did your rounds at night,
我有大约几分钟的时间来...
I had about a couple of minutes to myself to, uh...
做...做男孩做的那档子事
well, to, uh, to do what boys do.
那会是一天中 唯一让我感觉良好的时刻
And-and that would be the only time of day that I would feel anything good.
有一天晚上 我没能及时搞完
So this one night, uh, I couldn't get finished in time.
你发现我没穿裤子
And you caught me with my pants down.
狠狠地嘲笑了我一顿
You had a really, really good laugh at me.
记得吗
Remember?
就在那时 你给我起了射精小子的绰号
That's when you nicknamed me Squirt.
我必须对你说实话 马蒂
I got to be honest with you, Marty...
你真的伤害了我的感情
...you really hurt my feelings.
我很抱歉
I am very sorry.
覆水难收
What's done is done.
过去的就让它过去吧
Water under the bridge.
但先在那里站着
But stay there a sec.
我希望你现在就在我们面前自慰
I do want you to jerk off in front of us right now.
各位 过来
Hey, uh, guys, come on over here.
快点嘛
Come on. Yeah.
我们都会嘲笑你的 好吗
We're all gonna laugh at you. Okay?
是的
Yeah.
这样 你就会知道那是什么感觉 我想我会感觉好些
That way, you will know how it feels, and I think I'm gonna feel better.
祖国人
Homelander...
我真的非常抱歉
...I am really very sorry.
我知道
I know, I know.
谢谢
Thank you.
不过 别害羞 把裤子脱下来
Now, don't be shy. Take your pants down.
马上
Now.
这就对了嘛
That's the spirit.
马蒂 好像你在剥小蘑菇
Marty, it looks like you're shucking a little mushroom.
可怜的小东西
Oh, that poor little thing.
为他加油 快啊
Cheer for him. Come on.
射
Squirt. Squirt. Squirt.
开局不顺 是吧
Not off to a great start, huh?
这么着吧 我给你点动力
Tell you what, I'll give you a little motivation.
现在就硬起来 不然我就用激光把你的老二割掉
You get hard right now, or I'm gonna laser your dick off.
好吗
Okay?
这下有动力了吧
Something to play for now. Mm?
要么射 要么丢掉老二 马蒂
Use it or lose it, Marty.
生杀大权掌握在你自己手中
Your life is literally in your hands.
来吧 射精小子
Come on, Squirt.
好 多吐口水 马蒂
Yes! More spit, Marty,
多吐口水 会有用的
more spit. That'll work.
来吧 用力 漂亮
Come on! Put your fucking back into it. Attaboy.
我做不来
I can't.
来吧 马蒂
Come on, Marty!
听着 我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
好吧 没关系
Oh, oh, okay, okay, okay.
老实说 很多男人都会遇到这种情况
It's okay. Honestly, it-it happens to a-a lot of guys.
确实 当然我没有遇到过
Truly. Not me, of course.
射得不错啊 伙计
That's a fucking squirt, Marty.
你让我的靴子上 沾满了鸡巴的血 马蒂
Whoa, whoa! You're getting dick blood on my boots, Marty.
住手 约翰
Stop it, John.
芭芭拉
Barbara.
恐怕蛋糕已经化了
Um, the cake's melted, I'm afraid.
请让他摆脱痛苦吧
Please put him out of his misery.
我原谅你 马蒂
I forgive you, Marty.
我们可以私下聊聊吗
Can we talk in private?
好主意
That's a great idea.
我知道应该去哪谈
I know just the place.
在...我办公室里谈更舒服
Um, it's more comfortable in my office.
不 我认为这里更好
No, I think in here is better.
喜美子
Kimiko!
天哪
Holy shit!
该死
妈的
Oh, shit.
你是否记得
Do you remember?
你给我冰淇淋之后
After you offered me ice cream,
把我扔进了后备箱
then threw me into that trunk?
你带我去了营地
You took me to the camp,
把我拖进了战斗坑
dragged me into the fighting pit.
我要么战斗
I could either fight
要么就得死
or die.
你害我留下了这些疤痕
Then you left me with these.
我恨你
I hate you.
喜美子
Kimiko...
如果你们相信我身后皆为信徒
就说“是信徒” 好吗
是信徒
今晚 你们认识到了星光的真面目
Now, y'all heard a lot tonight about who Starlight really is.
但仍然没有看到面具背后 那个真正的禽兽
But you still haven't seen the true monster behind the mask.
事实...
And the truth...
要比你们想象的糟糕得多
...oh, it is so much worse than you could ever imagine.
不好了
Oh, no.
六个月前 星光去了一家诊所
Six months ago, Starlight visited a clinic.
但她并不是去检查身体
She wasn't going for a checkup.
搞什么鬼
What the fuck?
她发现自己怀孕了
She found out that she was pregnant,
跑去做了流产
and she had an abortion.
这些是我他妈的医疗记录吗
Are those my fucking medical records?
她从小就是基督徒
She was raised a Christian.
她是明是非的
She knew the difference between right and wrong.
她是明知故犯
She knew exactly what she was doing.
所以 怎么能让我相信那些青少年
So you won't tell me that those teens over there,
和她在一起是安全的  她可是个婴儿杀手啊
that they're safe with her. With that baby killer?
安妮 等等
Annie, wait.
你干什么呢
What do you think you're doing?
抱歉 我一定是迷路了
I'm sorry. I must've gotten lost.
- 糟了 - 你是谁
- Fucking hell. - Who are you?
法兰奇
Frenchie.
太尴尬了 我是鞭炮的铁杆粉丝
It is so embarrassing. I am Firecracker's biggest fan.
我只是想找她的衣服...
I was just looking for a souvenir...
嘿
她不要这个孩子 可以呀 供人收养嘛
She could have given it up for adoption.
但是 不 她谋杀了这孩子
But no. She murdered it.
你终于来...
So you finally came to deb--
居然之前以为我傲慢
How's that for "uppity," cracker?
住手
Stop.
看
Look.
星光暴怒 在直播电视节目上 胖揍鞭炮
走吧
Look.
第一个被拉下马的
First pebble down the mountain.
我们走吧
Let's get out of here.
走吧
Come on.
起来
Get up.
比利 快 站起来
Billy, come on, get up.
快点 比利
Come on. Billy.
你不能放弃
You don't get to quit.
起来
Get up!
真他妈的
Fucking hell.
- 怎么搞的  - 妈的
- What the fuck? - Oh, shit.
法兰奇
Frenchie!
不好 我的天 法兰奇
Oh, shit. Oh, my God. Frenchie.
- 这是他妈的怎么了  - 快 我们快走吧
-What the fuck happened? -Come on, let's get the fuck out of here.
好的
搞什么
What the fuck?
真有趣 我记得它要比这大得多
It's funny. I-I remember it being so much bigger.
你知道为什么 我以前把这里称为“坏房间”吗
You know why I used to call this The Bad Room?
这只是个房间 约翰 它既不好也不坏
It was just a room, John. It's neither good nor bad.
在门外时这么说很容易
That's easy to say from the other side of the door.
现在...
Now...
你回来就是为了折磨那些人吗
Did you come back here just to torment those people?
是不是感觉有点...
Doesn't that feel a little...
有点狭隘
a little small?
他们只是在执行 沃格尔鲍姆医生的命令
They were just following orders. Dr. Vogelbaum's, Stan Edgar's and mine.
- 史丹埃德加和我的命令 - 是的 但他们执行了那些命令
Yeah. But they followed them.
没有一个人有勇气 站出来说:“这是错误的”
Not one of them had the backbone to stand up and say, "This is wrong."
- 因为他们害怕 - 我还是个孩子
- 'Cause they were scared. - I was a child.
他们很害怕
They were scared.
知道嘛
You know...
你出生那天我就在场
I was there the day that you were born.
他们付给某个可怜的离家出走的人 两千美元的代孕费
They paid some poor runaway two grand to carry the embryo to term.
但你用激光从里面给她破了肚
But you lasered her guts open from the inside.
你升到空中 脐带还连着
You rose in the air with your umbilical cord still attached,
就像神话中的某种生物一样
like some creature out of myth...
也许是噩梦中的
or nightmare.
你出生时还杀死了 三名医生和一名护士
You killed three doctors and a nurse while you were at it.
此后 相信我 你就一发不可收拾了
And then, just trust me, it was downhill from there.
是的 从你降生起 每个人就都害怕你
So, yeah, yeah, everybody was terrified of you, from your first breath.
但你不怕
But you weren't?
我们没有你强大 从来都没有
We have no physical power over you. We never did.
你可以随时逃离这里
You could've broken out of here anytime you wanted.
我们是无法阻止你的 但你没有
We couldn't have stopped you. But you didn't.
因为你无法忍受
Because you couldn't stand the idea
我们会对你感到失望的想法
that we would be disappointed in you.
你需要认可和爱
Your need for approval and for love.
沃特请来了世界上最好的心理学家
Vought brought in the best psychologists in the world.
他们制定了方案 仔细地将这种需求植入于你
Developed the protocol to carefully engineer that need
令你听话
so that you would be obedient.
从很多方面来说 那是我们最大的成功
In many ways, that was our greatest success.
我不再需要它了
I don't need any of it anymore.
无论你对这里的其他员工 做什么都没关系
Doesn't matter what you do to me or the rest of the staff here.
你对爱的需求非常之深
Your need for love is so deep, it's so human,
这就是人性 你永远无法克服这一点
you'll never be able to overcome that.
你错就错在这里
That's where you're wrong.
我不是人类 我的儿子也不是
I'm not human. And neither is my son.
我会抚养他长大 让他知道这一点
And I'm going to raise him so that he knows it.
知道嘛
You know,
我真的很想告诉你 为什么我把这里称为“坏房间”
I really do want to share with you why I called this The Bad Room.
抵抗 #星光
嘿
Hey. Hey.
欢迎回来 你还好吗
Welcome back. You okay?
我觉得我最近总是在帮你包扎 我应该跟你的长官要钱才对
I feel like I've been fixing you up so much lately I should bill your HMO.
- 科林 拜托 - 我得扶你起来 来吧
- Colin, please. - All right, I got to get you up.
科林 好了 请别对我这么他妈的好
Colin, don't, please. Stop! Stop being so fucking nice to me!
那个人是我
It was me.
什么...什么是你
W-What was you?
是你
It was you?
对不起
I'm sorry.
你个该死的变态
You're a fucking psychopath.
来吧
Come on.
动手吧
Do it.
如果你再靠近我
If you come near me again...
我就他妈的杀了你
I'll fucking kill you.
你想见我
Yeah, so, you wanted to see me?
给你买了风味小镇的 炸泡菜和田园沙拉酱
Got you some of those fried pickles and ranch from Flavortown.
- 你就是这么道歉的吗  - 我需要你帮我个忙
- This your way of apologizing? - I need a favor.
我不理解你 一点都不理解
I don't get you, dude. Like, at all.
一开始 你就是个彻头彻尾的贱人
You start off, you're a total bitch,
然后你告诉我 我是更为优越的物种
and then you tell me I'm, like, a superior being--
我喜欢那样 然后你想干一炮
which of course I like and that you're down to pound,
- 显然 我会的 - 我知道
-which obviously I will-- -I know.
大多数人
Most people,
他们的大脑会一直生长到25岁左右 然后就永远停止生长
their brains grow till they're about 25, then stop forever.
我的不是 它不断地再生
Mine doesn't. It regenerates, constantly.
用刀捅进我的心脏 我就死了
Stab me in the heart, I die.
但是刺伤我的大脑 那个该死的小贱人会再长回来
But stab me in the brain and the little fucking bitch grows back.
我要你把这个放进我的体内
I want you to put this inside me.
这是我见过的 最糟糕的假阳具 但是...
That's the worst dildo I've ever seen, but--
不 插进我的眼睛里 这里
No. In my eye. Here.
我很想 但是...
I am down for, like, a lot, but...
这是暂时的
It's temporary.
你给我做额叶切除术
You give me a frontal lobotomy
之后的几个小时内 我就他妈的不必做自己了
and I don't have to fucking be me for a couple hours.
太他妈的恶心了
Uh, that's just... fucking gross.
我们看金姆和雷的视频时 我会让你把鸡巴插进我的屁眼里干我
I'll let you ass-fuck me while we watch the Kim and Ray J video.
你想把它插进哪里 这里 坐下
Okay, so where do you want me to put it? Just right there? Sit down.
别刺到眼球 我不想失明
Now, avoid the eye itself. I don't want to go blind.
现在...用锤子
Now, use the hammer.
锤子 他妈的
The hammer? Fuck.
轻敲
Tap, tap.
再敲
Again.
- 好了 - 好
- Okay. - Oh, sorry.
锤进去 现在...
Hammer down. Now...
- 刮 - 刮
- Scrape. - Scrape it?
把我该死的脑子刮个稀巴烂
Scrape my fucking brains out.
太怪了
That's weird.
好了 你可以把它取下来了
Okay, okay, okay. You can take it out.
天哪 你没事吧
Oh, God... Hey, are you okay?
嘿
So... Hey.
我为你准备了 另一道“风味小镇”的菜
I have another Flavortown for you.
- 我的小穴 - 好啊
- My pussy. - Yes.
风味小镇 盖伊菲耶里的厨房
纽曼对星光攻击行为的反应
今天发生的事件 不幸地证实了我的怀疑
Today's events have sadly confirmed my suspicions.
虽然我尊重当选总统辛格尔
While I respect President Elect Singer,
但看到他与星光结盟真是令人沮丧
it's disheartening to see him align himself with Starlight,
她明显是失控了
someone so clearly out of control.
更令人担忧的是
What's even more troubling is
我把星光当朋友 但是...
that I considered Starlight a friend. But her violent,
《言语治疗 失语症康复之星练习簿》
《言语治疗》
嘿
Hey.
天哪 你的腿怎么了
Oh, Jesus. What happened to your leg?
没关系 我没事
It's okay. I'm fine.
我看到了鞭炮的那件事 那个该死的混蛋
But, look, I saw the Firecracker thing. That fucking asshole.
不 我不应该失去理智
No, no, I shouldn't have lost it.
怎么可能不失去理智  那是最私密的信息
How could you not lose it? That was, like, the most private thing
只有我们俩知道 居然这样大肆广而告之
between you and me. And to fucking broadcast it like that,
- 简直他妈的没王法了 - 休伊 这样没有帮助 好吗
- that's a fucking violation. - Hughie. It's not helping, okay?
你说得对 对不起 你说得对 我很抱歉 对不起
Right, sorry, you're right. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
做出流产的决定 我很痛苦
I agonized over that decision.
痛苦不堪 而且
Agonized. And
你知道我很痛苦 我只是还没准备好要孩子
you know I did. I just wasn't ready.
我知道 我是说 我也没准备好
I know. I mean, neither was I.
现在 人们看着我时 无论他们是支持
And now when people look at me, whether they're...
评判 还是...还是愤怒
supportive or judging or-or angry,
我都必须重新体验那份痛苦
I have to relive it.
一遍又一遍 我妈...
Over and over and over again. And my mom...
你和她谈过吗
Have you talked to her?
她不肯给我回电话
She won't return my calls.
过来
Okay. Come here.
这不关她的事 好吗
It's none of her business. Okay?
这不关别人的事 只关你的事
It is nobody's business but yours.
该死 对不起 我必须接这通电话
Oh, shit. I'm sorry, I have to take this.
没关系 我...
It's okay. I, um,
我得给我爸取点东西
I have to pick up something for my dad.
- 我们稍后再谈 好吗  - 好的
- We'll talk later, okay? - Okay.
- 我爱你 - 我也爱你
- I love you. - Love you, too.
喂
Hello?
朋友之间会告知真相 而且...
You know, friends tell friends the truth, and...
《超人类控制法案》本会顺利通过
The Supe Control bill would've passed with flying colors.
但是在你今天这出之后呢
But after what you pulled today...
不妨称你这出为《变态星光 婴儿杀手将法案扼杀于摇篮中》
might as well call it the Psycho Starlight Baby-Killer bill.
你还在听吗
Are you still there?
对不起
I'm sorry.
抱歉并不能挽回 你刚刚毁掉的共和党选票
Sorry doesn't bring back all the Republican votes you just torched.
我不能再和你有任何关系了
I can't be affiliated with you anymore.
之前是胡说八道 对吧
It's bullshit, right?
你不会原谅我的
You're not gonna forgive me.
我就知道
Yeah. Thought so.
等等
Wait.
你说得对 我...
You're right, I...
我本来想说滚你妈的
I was gonna tell you to go fuck yourself.
但我改变了主意
But I changed my mind.
我们两清了
We're good.
你个该死的混蛋
You fucking dog-wanker.
天哪 你站在那里多久了
Jesus. How long have you been standing there?
反正什么都看到了
Long enough.
你怎么能这么做
How could you?
我没有...我不是为了他才这么做的
I-I didn't, I didn't do it for him.
我不想用自己的一生来憎恨任何人
I don't want to spend the rest of my life hating anybody.
你要用那东西做什么
What you gonna do with that, then?
你可能是唯一能理解的人
I mean, you're probably the only guy that would understand,
我要把它给我爸用
but I was going to give it to my dad.
休伊
Oh, Hughie.
听着 我知道 我知道这样做很疯狂 也很可怕
Look, I know. I know it's insane and terrible,
但我还有什么选择呢
but what other choice do I have?
只要他妈的别选这个 你个傻瓜
Any other fucking choice, you twat.
你是在告诉我
You're really telling me
如果你跟我爸处境相同 你不会用它吗
that you wouldn't take some if you were in his shoes?
因为你们俩的处境有点像 这一剂够你们俩用的
'Cause you kind of are. There's enough here.
它也能救你
It'd save you, too.
总比死于脑癌好 对吧
It's got to beat dying of brain cancer, right?
我已经用了
I already took some.
四个月前 从法兰奇的桌子上偷的
Nicked it out of Frenchie's desk four months ago.
以为它可以治愈我
Thought it might cure me.
天哪
Jesus.
你有超能力吗
Do you have powers?
没有 它只是把我的死期提前了
No. All it did was bring up the big day.
告诉你 放弃你要做的事吧
I'm telling you, quit while you're behind.
你只会让事情变得更糟
You'll only make matters worse.
在拖车里时 我是怎么了
What happened to me back there?
- 嘿 - 嘿
- Oh, hey. - Hey.
- 你还好吗  - 没事 只是绊倒了
- You okay? - Yeah, I just tripped.
他怎么样
How is he?
这个嘛
Well...
医生说很快就不行了
The doctor said any time now.
不
No, no.
我...
Um...
我只是需要透透气
I just need some air.
给
搞什么
What the fuck?
字幕翻译:张扬
创意监督 肖雪